A Guide to the Francis O. Holmes papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA129
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Correspondence, 1924-1979; 1; 8.4 Cubic Feet
  - William C. Price, 1950-1955 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - William C. Price, 1956-1957 1959-1962 1964 1966-1972 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Qua-Rak (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Frederika Quak, 1961
    - Quebec Society for the Protection of Plants, 1963
    - H.M. Quanjer, 1951
    - Avelina Quiaoit, 1962
    - William E. Rader, 1946
    - K. Radha, 1961 1963 1965
    - Kurt Radley, 1964
    - H. Ragetli, 1958
    - Geoffrey W. Rake, 1948-1951
  - Rama-Rams (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - K. Ramakrishnan, 1960
    - C.S. Ramamurthi, 1954
    - Conrado S. Ramirez, 1960-1963
    - O.D. Ramirez, 1959
    - John Ramsbottom, 1927
  - Ran-Raw (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Frederick V. Rand, 1927 1950
    - Rand McNally and Company, 1950-1951
    - G. Rangaswami, 1955
    - H.W. Rankin, 1941
    - W.H. Rankin, 1931 1949
    - Eugene T. Ransom, 1961
    - G.J. Rau, 1953
    - A.E. Raubitschek, 1942
    - Alan R. Raw, 1952
    - T.E. Rawlins, 1929-1930 1939 1941 1943 1952-1953
  - Ray-Raym (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Gordon N. Ray
    - S.P. Raychaudhuri, 1946 1952-1954 1956-1958 1963-1965
    - W.B. Raymer
  - Red-Regin (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Donald Reddick, 1933 1938-1939
    - D.V.R. Reddy, 1967
    - G. Redei, 1959
    - E.L. Reeves, 1940
    - Regina Laudis Monastery, Bethlehem, CT, 1972-1975
  - Regis-Ret (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Registrar, University of Sydney, 1954
    - I. Reichert, 1955 1958
    - M.E. Reichmann, 1968
    - Hobart A. Reiman, 1956
    - Herman J. Reitz, 1956-1960 1969
    - M. Van Rensselaer, 1938
    - D.F. Retief, 1941
  - Rex-Rey (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Edgar G. Rex, 1938-1939 1942 1956
    - Pratt Rexford, 1942-1943
    - George B. Reynard, 1938 1941 1948
  - Rh-A. Rich (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - A.J. Rhodes, 1951-1952
    - Avery Rich, 1955 1958-1960 1962 1965-1966 1968-1969 1971-1972
  - S. Rich-Rie (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Saul Rich, 1953-1955 1958
    - B.L. Richards, 1938 1950
    - M.C. Richards, 1941 1943
    - Charles M. Rick, 1951
    - F.W. Rickard, 1950
    - Ed Rickert, 1961
    - Harold W. Rickett, 1944
    - Arthur R. Riddle, 1928
    - J. Rietsema, 1960
  - A.J. Riker, 1940 1942-1944 1946-1947 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Ril-Riv (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - E.A. Riley, 1957
    - Raymond Ring, 1950
    - Arturo Riollano, 1941 1945
    - Thomas M. Rivers, 1926 1928-1929 1939 1953-1955
  - Roa-Roch (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Curtis W. Roane, 1964
    - Sheila N. Robb, 1961
    - William J. Robbins, 1938 1951 1959 1964
    - W. Rei Robbins, 1951-1952
    - Alice Robert, 1961
    - Catherine Roberts, 1940
    - Daniel A. Roberts, 1951 1955 1960
    - Albert D. Robertson, 1936 1943 1948
    - Richard S. Robertson, 1956
    - William F. Rochow, 1953 1955 1961
  - Rock-Rol (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - David Rockefeller, 1952
    - John D. Rockefeller, Jr., 1935
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1949 1954 1957
    - Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research, 1935 1949 1951
    - Rockefeller University, 1972
    - S.D. Rodenberg, 1956
    - H.A. Rodenhiser, 1948
    - Jose Rodriguez Rivera, 1958-1959
    - P.A. Rodrigo, 1962
    - Stanfield Rogers, 1953
    - G. Roland, 1954-1955 1967
    - Duane Roller, 1954
    - Reed Rollins, 1950
  - Arturo Roque, 1938 1942 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Arturo Roque, 1946-1948 1951-1952 1955 1957-1958 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Arturo Roque, 1959-1961 1963 1967-1968 1972 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - del Ros-Rose (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Ma. Salome del Rosario, 1960-1963
    - Francisco Rosenbusch, 1951-1952
    - Mark J. Rosenfeld
    - Eugen Rosenkranz, 1959
    - Martin Rosenthal, 1962
  - A. Frank Ross, 1941-1943 1947-1951 1953-1954 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - A. Frank Ross, 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - A. Frank Ross, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - A. Frank Ross, 1958-1960 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - A. Frank Ross, 1961-1963 1965 1967 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Ross-Ryz (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Jeanne Ross, 1945-1946
    - Hans von Rothkirch, 1961-1963
    - E. Roubaud, 1935
    - Peyton Rous, 1940
    - F. Rousenbusch
    - Steiner Rudolf, 1960
    - George D. Ruehle, 1944-1945
    - Gail E. Rumley, 1951
    - Bertrand Russell, 1959
    - Louise M. Russell, 1951
    - V.L. Ryzhkov, 1953-1954 1958 1964
  - Sab-Sal (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Albert Sabin, 1937-1938 1948-1949 1955-1956
    - Florence R. Sabin, 1935
    - W.E. Sackston, 1962 1969
    - T.S. Sadasivan, 1964
    - K. Sakimura, 1947-1949 1951 1953-1963
    - Redcliffe N. Saloman, 1929 1933
  - Sams-G. Samuel (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - R.W. Samson, 1928 1940 1942
    - Geoffrey Samuel, 1930-1939
  - Geoffrey Samuel, 1941 1944 1946-1951 1953-1955 1964 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Sand-Sant (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - C. Sanders, 1953
    - H. Sandon, 1926 1930-1931 1936 1942
    - E.P. Sandsten, 1937
    - E. Sankevitsch, 1953
    - Eva Santillan, 1961-1962 1964
    - Vincent Santilli, 1959
  - Sar-Schr (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Sargent, 1954
    - W.A. Sawyer, 1938
    - Karl Sax, 1943
    - Lawrence A. Schaal, 1952
    - Carl C. Schaefer, 1942
    - Asa A. Schaeffer, 1957
    - John F. Schafer, 1964
    - P.K. Schenk, 1963
    - Lyman G. Schermerhorn, 1938 1951-1952
    - K. Schmelzer, 1963 1965
    - Kenneth C. Schmitt, 1957
    - Waldo L. Schmitt, 1938
    - Irving R. Schneider, 1958
    - G. Schramm, 1956
    - Jacob R. Schramm, 1960
    - Ernst J. Schreiner, 1956
    - W.T. Schroeder, 1947 1953 1958
  - Schu-Sev (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - John Schule, Jr., 1970
    - E.S. Schultz, 1930-1932 1938 1943 1945 1948-1949 1953 1960
    - David Schweizer, 1951
    - Science, 1964 1966
    - Science Press Printing, Co., 1941
    - Science Service, 1965
    - Scientific American, 1960
    - Scientific Monthly, 1950
    - D.H. Scott, 1960
    - Howard Scott, 1958
    - Scottish Horticultural Research Institute, 1955
    - L.B. Sebrell, 1924
    - O.P. Sehgal, 1957
    - Francisco Sein, Jr., 1947
    - I.W. Selman, 1959
    - H.H.P. Severin, 1948
  - Shaf-D. Shaw (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - John Shafer, Jr., 1945
    - S. Moir Shah, 1966
    - W.A. Shands, 1943
    - P. Shanta, 1961 1964-1965
    - Seymour Shapiro, 1953
    - Dhanesh C. Sharma, 1954 1956-1958 1963-1965
    - Eleanor Sharpley, 1955
    - Dorothy E. Shaw, 1961-1964 1968
  - H. Shaw-Sho (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - J.K. Shaw, 1943-1944
    - J. Ralph Shay, 1964-1965
    - F.M.L. Sheffield, 1963
    - Oved Shifriss, 1947-1948 1959
    - Alex L. Shigo, 1966
    - N.S. Shirlow, 1949-1950
    - R.N. Shoemaker, 1957
    - R.E. Shope, 1938 1956
  - Shor-Silb (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - John W. Shorter, 1946
    - R.W. Shuel, 1959
    - George H. Shull, 1937-1938
    - M.C. Shurtleff, 1947-1965
    - Albert Siegel, 1958-1959
    - M. Michael Sigel, 1952
    - H.D. Sikand, 1961-1962
    - Gustave Silber, 1964
  - Sigma Xi, 1958-1959 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Karl M. Silberschmidt, 1938-1939 1941 1944 1948 1958-1960 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Webster H. Sill, Jr., 1962 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Webster H. Sill, Jr., 1963 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Webster H. Sill, Jr., 1964-1966 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Sim-Sin (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Robert Sim, 1926
    - N.W. Simmonds, 1956
    - E.M. Simmons, 1949
    - Charles E. Simon, 1925
    - John N. Simons, 1953-1954 1956
    - Geddes W. Simpson, 1936 1951
    - Jennie L.S. Simpson, 1954
    - W.R. Simpson, 1960
    - Gregg M. Sinclair, 1946
    - Wayne A. Sinclair, 1965
    - G.P. Singh, 1957-1958
    - Rajendra Singh, 1964
    - W.R. Singleton, 1950-1951 1953
  - Sis-Sly (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Hugh D. Sisler, 1960 1962-1963
    - B.F. Skinner, 1958
    - Calvin L. Skinner, 1952
    - R.E. Skiver, 1958
    - Vladimir Skoric, 1933
    - W.H, Skrdla, 1957-1959 1968
    - J.T. Slykhuis, 1962-1964
  - Smil-J. Smith (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - E.W. Smillie, 1943-1945 1950 1952 1955
    - David T. Smith, 1952
    - Edric B. Smith, 1936 1938-1942 1944 1948-1952
    - Floyd F. Smith, 1955 1960 1976
    - J. Henderson Smith, 1930-1932 1939
  - Kenneth M. Smith, 1939-1941 1946-1949 1951-1960 1962 1964 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - P. Smith-Sn (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Paul G. Smith, 1947-1949 1952 1954 1957 1960
    - Theobald Smith, 1934
    - T.E. Smith, 1936
    - Smithsonian Institution, 1962-1963
    - Smithsonian Institution - International Exchange Service, 1954 1965
    - Stanislaw F. Snieszko, 1948 1951 1955
    - Robert J. Snyder, 1968
  - Soc-Spec (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Society for the Advancement of Research, 1964
    - M. Acosta Solis, 1943
    - F. Solymosy, 1957
    - David Sompolinsky, 1950
    - Robert K. Soost, 1956 1959 1964
    - Grover Sowell, Jr., 1963
    - D. Spear, 1970
    - Sterling S. Speake, 1943
    - William S. Spector, 1952 1955
  - Spen-Sgu (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Ernest L. Spencer, 1934 1941 1944-1946 1951-1952 1957 1961 1968 1972
    - George E. Spencer, 1962
    - Manuel Sproat, 1962
    - Thomas Sproston, 1943 1960
    - E.R. Squibb and Sons, 1954
  - Stad-Star (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - L.J. Stadler, 1946
    - Gerald Stahel, 1932 1934
    - Elvin C. Stakman, 1943 1955
    - Elvin C. Stakman Award Fund Committee, 1953
    - A.F.B. Standfast, 1955
    - Wendell M. Stanley, 1955
    - Robert L. Starkey, 1942
  - Ordway Starnes, 1951-1953 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Stec-Steinh (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Stechert-Hafner, Inc., 1955
    - J. Murray Steele, 1937
    - Adin P. Steenland, 1942
    - Russell L. Steere, 1950 1960
    - William C. Steere, 1954
    - W.N. Steil, 1949
    - F. Steinecke, 1936
    - Edward A. Steinhaus, 1947 1949-1951 1953 1964
  - Steink-Stew (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Joseph Steinke, 1955
    - W.A. Stephen, 1968-1969
    - J.M. Steven, 1953
    - Russell B. Stevens, 1950 1971
    - Frederick J. Stevenson, 1951 1953
    - John A. Stevenson, 1961
    - A.M. Stewart, 1953
    - Florence M. Stewart, 1940 1950 1954-1956
    - James J. Stewart, 1958 1963
  - Stod-Stol (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - E.M. Stoddard, 1941
    - G.W. Stokes, 1962
    - Jacob L. Stokes, 1945
    - Louise Stoll, 1957
  - Warren N. Stoner, 1949-1954 1956-1959 1962 1964 1971 1979 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - H.H. Storey, 1928-1929 1931 1933-1934 1936-1940 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - H.H. Storey, 1941-1950 1958 1961 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Stou-Str (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Richard F. Stoufer, 1959 1963
    - A.B. Stout, 1956
    - Loren H. Stover, 1957
    - R.H. Stover, 1949-1951 1955
    - George Streisinger, 1954
    - E.F. Striplin, 1951
    - Lee A. Strong, 1939
  - Barbara A. Sutphin, 1954 1957-1959 1961-1962 1973 1975 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Sutt-Sz (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - W.S. Sutton, 1957
    - Henry K. Svenson, 1938-1939
    - Mark H. Swartz, 1963
    - Howard Swift, 1960
    - Roger U. Swingle, 1938
    - Edward S. Sylvester, 1948 1953
    - R.H. Symons, 1962
    - Jayne Szaz, 1961
    - Adam Szcyzygiel, 1959
  - Tab-Tar (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - John Taber, 1947
    - Ichigo Takagi, 1930
    - Willaim N. Takahashi, 1929 1931 1943 1949-1951 1953-1955 1958
    - William H. Taliaferro, 1925 1952 1959-1960
    - James Tammen, 1964
    - Shoichi Tanaka, 1958-1959
    - A.C. Tarjan, 1954 1958 1960 1962 1964 1966 1968
    - S.A.J. Tarr, 1952-1953
  - Tat-The (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - H. Douglas Tate, 1941-1943
    - Edward L. Tatum, 1957
    - J.J. Taubenhaus, 1930
    - Amparo M. Tayag, 1961
    - G.G. Taylor, 1948
    - Gordon S. Taylor, 1953 1955-1956 1963-1965
    - Richard M. Taylor, 1950
    - Robert H. Taylor, 1965
    - David S. Teakle, 1963-1964
    - Technical Information Service, USAEC, 1954
    - A.C. Tegethoff, 1964
    - Carl TenBroeck, 1939-1941 1944 1947
    - M.F. Ternovsky, 1938
    - Thet Su, 1961
  - Thorn-Thorn (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - H. Earl Thomas, 1944 1952-1953 1955
    - W.D. Thomas, Jr., 1957
    - A.E. Thompson, 1955
    - Ross C. Thompson, 1952
    - Randall L. Thompson, 1952
    - A.D. Thomson, 1955 1957 1960 1963
    - Fred C. Thomson, 1966
    - Gerald Thorne, 1929-1930
  - H.H. Thornberry, 1939-1942 1948-1951 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - H.H. Thornberry, 1955 1957 1959-1961 1963 1965-1966 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Thr-Tip (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - J.M. Thresh, 1958
    - T.H. Thung, 1936 1940 1946 1951-1954 1958-1959
    - Warner H. Thurlow, 1955
    - B.D. Thyr, 1964
    - Joseph S. Tidd, 1952
    - Evelyn B. Tilden, 1926
    - Oswald Tippo, 1950-1951
  - Tis-Tow (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Wendell H. Tisdale, 1947
    - John L. Toevs, 1939
    - Tomato Genetics Cooperative, undated
    - J.A. Tomlinson, 1958
    - C.M. Tompkins, 1939-1940 1954
    - F.W. Toovey, 1957 1960
    - Theodore C. Torrey, 1951
    - G.R. Townsend, 1935
  - Tra-Tys (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - William Trager, 1939 1962
    - Lillia M.D. Trask, 1935-1937
    - Blanca Alicia Traversi, 1950
    - S.F. Trelease, 1950
    - J.H. Tremaine, 1959 1961
    - Alfredo Tribolet Navarro, 1940
    - Oliver J. Troster, 1964
    - A.R. Trotter, 1939
    - J.L. Troutman, 1957 1966
    - Bernard Trouvelot, 1928
    - C.M. Tucker, 1939 1948-1949 1953
    - John Tuite, 1959
    - Thomas B. Turner, 1945-1946
    - H.M. Tysdal, 1954
  - Ul-Up (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Arnold J. Ullstrup, 1939 1961
    - Dioscoro Umali, 1960-1964 1966
    - E.J. Underwood, 1953
    - Union of South Africa, 1947
    - United States Atomic Energy Commission, 1954
    - United States Internal Revenue, 1965
    - United States Rubber Company, 1945
    - University of Adelaide, 1954
    - University of Hawaii, 1947
    - University of Florida Press, 1964
    - University of Missouri, 1960
    - University Microfilms, 1955
    - B.N. Uppal, 1934 1940 1955
  - Vale-Vall (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Victor C. Valenzuela, 1961
    - W.D. Valleau, 1929 1936-1938 1940-1945 1948-1952
    - Jose Vallega, 1961
  - van G-van R (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - P. van der Goot, 1939-1940
    - J.E. van der Plank, 1956 1961
    - J.P.H. van der Want, 1952 1956
    - H.B. van Dyke, 1938
    - J.H. van Emden, 1958
    - L.C. van Loon, 1969
    - J. van Overbeek, 1944
    - Maunsel van Resselaer, 1938
  - C.E. van Rooyen, 1949-1955 1959-1960 1962 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - van R-Vav (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - E. van Slogteren, 1952
    - Cesar Vargas, 1943-1944
    - Mary Varghese, 1965
    - Eugene H. Varney, 1953 1957-1958 1960
    - R.S. Vasudeva, 1951-1952 1959
    - Edward K. Vaughan, 1938
    - N.I. Vavilov, 1930 1936 1938
  - Vel-Voe (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - J. Velez-Fortuno, 1959
    - Frans Verdoorn, 1939-1941 1944 1950
    - G.S. Verma, 1951
    - Hans Vermeulen, 1962-1963
    - Betty Vernon, 1965
    - G. Verplancke, 1940
    - Veterans Administration, 1932 1965
    - Ramon T. Vicente, 1961-1962
    - K. Vijayalakshmi, 1964-1965
    - Carl G. Vinson, 1934
    - Walter J. Virgin, 1939-1941 1943-1944
    - J. Voelcker, 1948
    - Bruce R. Voeller, 1970
  - Wad-Walke (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - B.L. Wade, 1937
    - Bryce Wadley, 1941
    - H. Keith Wagnon, 1964-1965
    - F.T. Wahlen, 1957
    - Selman A. Waksman, 1949 1954 1963
    - Duard Walker, 1957
    - Edgar R. Walker, 1971
    - J.C. Walker, 1943 1945 1947 1949 1956 1958-1959
    - Jerry T. Walker, 1962-1966
  - Walko-Wan (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Charles Walkof, 1945
    - George B. Wallace, 1934
    - J.M. Wallace, 1934
    - R.J. Wallace, 1950
    - G.W. Walls, 1948
    - J.M. Walter, 1949 1954 1956-1957
    - Hsiung Wan, 1965-1966
  - Wane-Wat (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - M.J. Wanelik, 1965
    - Pingnan Wang, 1952
    - War Manpower Commission, 1974
    - H.E. Warmke, 1939
    - Charles O. Warren, 1956
    - Harriette B. Wasser, 1953
    - W.L. Waterhouse, 1943-1945
    - Marion A. Watson, 1954 1959 1965
    - R.D. Watson, 1947 1951
  - Wea-Wein (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Gerald M. Weaver, 1959
    - Joseph F. Webb, Jr., 1932
    - Raymon E. Wevv, 1960
    - George F. Wever, 1953-1954
    - Paul V.V. Wever, 1950-1951 1955-1956
    - Leslie T. Webster, 1936-1937 1939-1940 1942
    - C.A. Weigel, 1943
    - J.H. Weinberger, 1948
    - Marvin Weintraub, 1958-1963
  - Weise-F. Weiss (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Jaroslav Weiser, 1958-1959
    - Freeman A. Weiss, 1936-1937 1939-1945 1947-1950
  - H. Weiss-Wellm (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Harry B. Weiss, 1939 1941
    - Gerard S. Weissman, 1949
    - D.M. Weller, 1939
    - Edwin J. Wellhausen, 1945
    - Frederick L. Wellman, 1932 1934-1944 1947 1950-1953 1955-1959 1963-1964 1967 1970
  - Wells-Whip (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - H.D. Wells, 1953
    - Phillip G. Wells, 1936
    - Wen-chun Ho, 1941
    - H. Wenholz, 1938-1940
    - C.C. Wernham, 1939 1966
    - W.H. Weston, 1964
    - W.H. Wheeler, 1951
    - H.H. Whetzel, 1939-1940 1943
    - O.C. Whipple, 1939 1942
  - Whit-G.F. White (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Douglas M. Whitaker, 1956-1963
    - Thomas W. Whitaker, 1934 1936 1945 1952
    - C.T. White, 1931
    - F. White, 1961
    - George A. White, 1978-1979
    - G.F. White, 1925
  - N.H. White-Whits (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Neville H. White, 1952-1955
    - Richard P. White, 1931
    - Marvin D. Whitehead, 1950
    - Roger A. Whitehead, 1963-1964
    - W.E. Whitehouse, 1938 1944-1945 1948 1950 1956
    - Jesse Whitsit, 1930
  - Wild-C. Wilson (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - P. Wildy, 1966
    - R.E. Wilkinson, 1950 1955 1957-1958 1964
    - Drenka Willen, 1961
    - J.J. Williaman, 1952
    - A.J. Williams, 1953
    - Ann S. Williams, 1957
    - Charlotte Williams, 1965
    - Llewelyn Williams, 1937
    - R.E. Williams, 1948
    - Williams & Wilkins Company, 1945 1948
    - R.S. Willison, 1953
    - Charles M. Wilson, 1948
  - E.E. Wilson-Wit (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - E.E. Wilson, 1958-1960
    - Perry Wilson, 1937
    - V.E. Wilson, 1961
    - S.P. Wiltshire, 1944 1951 1953
    - S.A. Wingard, 1928
    - J. Winsser, 1952
    - Nash N. Winstead, 1957-1959
    - H.F. Winters, 1956
    - G.A. Wistreich, 1968
    - Guenter Wittmann, 1957
    - G.L. Wittrock, 1937
  - Wol-Wood (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - George N. Wolcott, 1945
    - Frederick A. Wolf, 1938
    - H.S. Wolfe, 1941 1944
    - Jessie I. Wood, 1953
    - W. Richard Woodland, 1971
    - Mark W. Woods, 1938-1946 1955 1971-1975
  - Wool-Wye (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Donna Woolf, 1961
    - D. Wayne Woolley, 1947 1963
    - G.E. Wooliams, 1937
    - Sterling Wortman, 1962
    - Charles M. Wright, 1947 1951
    - Don Wright, 1967
    - Vedder Wright, 1939-1940
    - Helen M. Wrigley, 1948
    - R.W.G. Wyckoff
  - Ya-Ys (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Masaki Yamamoto, 1955-1956
    - C.E. Yarwood, 1953-1955 1962-1966 1968
    - Paul Yagyu, 1948
    - David A. Young, 1961
    - P.A. Young, 1940 1953
    - Robert E. Young, 1956
    - S.G. Younkin, 1944 1948 1953
    - Ysmael Steel Manufacturing Company, 1962
  - Za-Zu (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Milton Zaitlin, 1965-1966
    - W.J. Zaumeyer, 1953
    - S.M. Zeller, 1941
    - George Z. Zentmyer, 1945 1966
    - V.M. Zhdanov, 1954-1955 1958 1962
    - James E. Ziegler, 1943
    - Quentin Zielinski, 1944
    - Ray W. Zimmerman, 1948
    - L. Zobrist, 1949
    - G. Zotta, 1925-1926
    - Bert M. Zuckerman, 1956 1958 1964
- Published papers
  Arrangement
  The numbers on these volumes are the numbers which appear in F.O. Holmes' bibliography (Table of Contents).
  - Herpetomonad flagellate in milkweed in the United States. Sc. D. dissertation at the School of Hygiene and Public Health, Johns Hopkins University., 1925; a; Typescript. (Box 22)
  - Handbook of phytopathogenic viruses. Minneapolis, MN, Burgess Publishing Co., 1939; 40; 221 pages.
    Separated Materials
    Relocated to RAC Library August 9, 1988.
  - Handbook of phytopathogenic viruses. Minneapolis, MN, Burgess Publishing Co. Revised printing., 1941; 40a
  - The filterable viruses. In: Breed, R.S.; Murray, E.G.D.; Hitchens, A.P. Bergey's manual of determinative bacteriology. 6th ed. Baltimore, MD, Williams & Wilkins., 1948; 52; p. 1125
  - The filterable viruses. Baltimore, MD, Williams & Wilkins., 1948; 52a; p. 1127-1286, i-xxiii.
  - F.O. Holmes Collected Reprints, 1923-1972
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Added to the Collection June 1985.